what can Ukraine give us we are
что Украина нам может дать мы вам ничего
not obliged to offer you anything we will take the
не обязаны предлагать мы заберём
territories for ourselves you want peace for the sake of peace
территории себе вы хотите мир ради мира
I asked you do you need territories or
я же спросил вам нужны территории или
peace you say: "Peace" well that's it
мир вы говорите: "Мир" ну так всё
get out of Crimea Donetsk Lugansk yes
выходите из Крыма Донецка Луганска да
get out of Kursk region:
выходите из Курской области:
Belgorod Bryansk Rostov
Белгородской Брянской Ростовской
Voronezh and Krasnodar region and everyone
Воронежской и Краснодарского края и всё
who does not agree to live under Ukraine
кто не согласен жить под Украиной
leaves for example to Altai region
уезжает например в Алтайский край
Vladivostok there is Kolyma
Владивосток есть Колыма
hello priest where are you from about
здравствуйте попик вы откуда о
Popok from Krasnodar from Kuban it's cool I am
Попок с Краснодара с Кубани прикольно я
from the city of Khmelnitsky what are you talking about I do
из города Хмельницкий о чём общаетесь
n't know about anything interesting
не знаю о чём-нибудь интересном
interesting doesn't it seem to you that America
интересном вам не кажется что Америка
the Anglo-Saxons deliberately set two
англосаксы специально стравили два
Slavic peoples against each other to be exterminated
славянских народа на истребление
forced Putin to attack Ukraine so that the
заставили Путина напасть на Украину
Slavs would kill the Slavs well everything is much more
чтобы славяне убивали славян
complicated
ну там всё сложнее
there everything is a lot well there was such an idea of
намного там всё много ну была такая идея
course but everything did not go according to plan
конечно но всё пошло не по плану
but it seems to me of course
но мне кажется конечно
that only the Anglo-Saxons benefit from this
что от этого выигрывают только
because look the Slavs
англосакцы потому что смотри славяне
are killing the Slavs the Anglo-Saxons are rubbing their hands
убивают славян англосакцы потирают руки
well yes to them in principle
ну да им в принципе
and why then Putin plays into the hands of
а зачем Путин тогда играет на руку
the Anglo-Saxons
англосаксон
and what do you think well I think yes I
а вы как думаете ну я же думаю да я
think that this Why why do the Slavs
думаю что это Зачем зачем славяне
kill the Slavs well because And you
убивают славян ну потому что А вы
think And you think well Russians and
считаете А вы считаете ну русских и
Ukrainians are a brotherly brotherly people yes they are a
украинцей братский братский народ да это
brotherly people we look we are together we are
братский народ мы смотри мы вместе мы
all Slavic peoples Russians Ukrainians
все славянские народы русские украинцы
Belarusians Estonians Kazakhs fought against Hitler
белорусы эстонцы казахи против Гитлера
once no no Estonians did not
воевали когда-то да нене эстонцы не
fight they fought this is all for the whole
воевали воевали это все на весь
Soviet
Советский
Union not in Ribalka these are all our brothers these are
Союзни не в Рибалке это все наши братья
all our brothers we in the Soviet
это все наши братья на мы в Советском
Union everyone built everyone lived in harmony and so on and so
Союзе все строили все жили дружно и так
forth the Americans differ
дальше американцы разли
look the Americans well I agree that Yeltsin
смотри американцы ну согласен что Ельцин
and Gorbachev American agents destroyed the
и Горбачёв американские агенты развалили
Soviet Union Gorbachev withdrew troops from
Советский Союз горбачёв вывел войска из
East Germany destroyed the
Восточной Германии развалил в
Berlin Wall in eighty-nine
восемьдесят девятом берлинскую стену
then withdrew troops from Poland
дальше вывел войска из Польши
Czechoslovakia Hungary NATO went there right away and
Чехосовакии Венгрии туда зашло сразу
then in collusion with the Anglo-Saxons they
НАТО да дальше по сговору с англосаксами
destroyed the Soviet Union Yeltsin and
развалили Советский Союз Ельцин и
Gorbachev, everything is calm, well, do you believe
Горбачёв да всё спокойно ну ты веришь
that all these republics could simply separate
что просто могли отделиться все эти
if the Soviet Union
республики если б Советский Союз Москва
had wanted, Moscow would have snapped, they would have brought in troops and
захотела щёлкнула б вели б войска да
arrested all these rebels who
арестовали всех этих мятежников которые
declared independence there and that's it. In
там провозгласили независимость и всё
1968, they somehow flew to Prague,
в шестьдесят восьмом году в Прагу как-то
took an oak tree to Moscow, took it away,
прилетели дубчика забрали в Москву
tanks were brought to Prague and that's it, and then they
увезли танки в Прагу ввели и всё и а тут
kind of let Ukraine go, Kazakhstan came in, Kazakhstan
как бы отпустили Украину приба Казахстан
never left the
вообще Казахстан ниоткуда не выходил из
Soviet Union, everyone left the Soviet Union,
Советского Союза все вышли из Советского
Kazakhstan was the only one left there, like,
Союза казахстан там один остался такой:
"Well, okay, so are we" and Elson said,
"Ну ладно мы тоже" да ельсон сказал:
"Take as much independence as you want,
"Берите независимости сколько хотите
how much can you take out" and so it
сколько вы вывезете" да да вот и
turns out that the Americans immediately build,
получается что американцы сразу стройте
just build a normal state, the
только стройте нормальное государство
Americans threaten
американцы угрожайте
Russia, the Americans, not the Americans, immediately
России американцы не американцы сразу
entered all the educated states,
зашли во все ээ образованные государства
including Russia, well, agree that
в том числе и в Россию ну согласись что
under Yeltsin, the entire apparatus of the White House, the entire apparatus of the White House was
при Ельцине весь аппарат Белого дома
supervised by the Americans, the entire sixth
курировался американцами весь шестой
floor was American advisers, yes, all of these,
этаж был американские советники да все
they promoted these  Chubaytsev
эти они продвигали этих чубайцев
Yalinsky and so on yes yes yes correct correct
ялинских и так дальше дадада правильно
correct Yeltsin said:
правильно правильно ельцин говорил:
"America will help us abroad" will
"Америка заграница нам поможет" поможет
yes that's what he said yes he
да это что он говорил да он
danced Kalinkumalinka there kissed with
танцевал Калинкумалинку там целовался с
these Clintons yes well so what
этими Клинтонами да вот ну и что
helped we already we already understood that it won't
помогли мы уже по мы уже поняли что не
help look no the whole dollar you
поможет смотри нет весь доллар вас
were put on the dollar and look Russia
посадили на доллар и посмотри Россия до
still hasn't given up the dollar you have the
сих пор не отказалась от доллара у вас
head of the Central Bank who is
глава Центробанка кто
Nabiullina Elvira Nabiullina yes Elvira
набиулина эльвира Набиулина да эльвира
Elvira Sakhibzadovna yes the question is yes how
эльвира Сахибзадовна да вопрос да как бы
many questions Russians already have for her and
сколько уже к ней вопросов у россиян и
for some reason they don't remove her why well
почему-то её не снимают почему
because there is still a dependence on the Fed
ну потому что есть ещё с ФРС зависимость
correct because Yes she is a creature of the
правильно потому что Да она креатура
US federal audit system
федеральной ревизирной системы США
correct Trump is shaking things up now and I
правильно трамп сейчас шатает и вот мне
wonder what they are
интересно о чём сейчас
agreeing on now because now
договариваются вот потому что сейчас
serious talks are going on here Vikov
серьёзные разговоры идут вот Виков
Vitka Vitkov Vitkov he came and I
Витька Витьков витьков он приезжал и я
think there is already talk about this
думаю там уже вот об этом идёт речь
because well they will shake this whole
потому что ну будут шатать эту всю
system
систему
and the Fed is a private private company,
и ФРС - это же частная частная компания
yes, they are like that So look, they did it
да они же как сде Так смотри они сделали
in America then they came up with the Federal
в Америке тогда придумали Федеральную
Reserve System as a private company, it is a
резервную систему как частная компания
private bank that prints money
это частный банк который печатает деньги
for the USA, this is completely absurd, and in Russia they
для США это вообще абсурд да и в России
made the same model, your
сделали такую же самую модель у вас
Central Bank is an analogue of the Fed, the Federal
Центробанк - это аналог ФРС Федеральной
Reserve System, yes, as a branch, a
резервной системы да ну как филиал
branch, yes, yes, look, by the way, you do
филиал да да посмотри у вас кстати у вас
n’t write money, what do you write on
не пишутся деньги у вас что пишется на
banknotes, a ticket of the Bank of Russia, have you noticed,
банкнотах билет Банка России ты замечал
get it out, you have some kind of bill, just
вот достань есть есть у тебя купюра
for fun, you have to go, take it,
вот ради интереса надо идти возьми
look, I’m interested, I don’t have one,
посмотри мне интересно у меня нету
why, well, I saw on the Internet that you have a
почему ну я видел в интернете у вас
ticket of the Bank of Russia, can you show me,
пишет билет Банка России можешь показать
yes, you have such a ticket of the Bank of Russia, well,
да есть такой билет Банка России ну
show me, how interesting, is there at least one
покажи как мне интересно есть хоть одна
bill that doesn’t have a ticket of the
купюра на которой не написано билет
Bank of Russia written on it, oh, I don’t want to get up,
Банка России ой не хочу вставать надо
I have to go, well, it’s easier for me, it’s easier to just rant, well, it
идти ну я мне проще проще погурить
just turns out that you do
хорошо да просто получается что у вас
n’t even have money backed by something, yes, but
даже не деньги подкреплённые чем-то да а
you have tickets, that is, as you know, a
у вас билеты то есть это как знаешь
ticket for a tram, tickets, they are not
билет в на трамвай билеты они ничем не
obliged to anything, you understand that  they give you tickets and it
обязаны понимаешь это вам дают билеты
says: "Ticket of the Bank of Russia" that
так и написано: "Билет Банка России" то
is, this is done on purpose because
есть это специально делается потому что
if it is money, yes, money was written out
если это деньги да там выписались деньги
there, for example, 1,000 rubles, and this is how a ticket of the
там например 1.000 руб а так это пишется
Bank of Russia is written like a ticket of an
билет Банка России как вот билет
opera house, and this is a ticket of the Bank of Russia of a
оперного театра а это билет Банка России
private company, look, by the way, it is
частной компании посмотри кстати
interesting
интересно
no, I understand, I understand, I understand all this, yes, I
нет я понимаю я понимаю я всё это
also thought about this, yes,
понимаю да тоже думал над этим да сейчас
now it turns out, yes, there is a dependence on the
сейчас получается да есть зависимость
Central Bank, but I think that when the Fed
Центробанк но я думаю что когда ФРС
collapses, the Central Bank will already be
развалится то Центробанк уже будет
sovereign, I do not think that the Fed will collapse
суверенный я не думаю что ФРС развалится
because look, the Morgans, the Rockefellers, yes,
потому что смотри Морганы Рокфелеры да
who, in principle, oversee the Fed, yes, they
которые в принципе курируют ФРС да они
exist, I, yes, they, yes, they, I Kennedy was also killed for a reason, it is
есть я да они да да они Я Кеннеди же
true, Kennedy
тоже убили не просто так правда Кеннеди
was killed, he also raised the issue of the
убили он же тоже поднял вопрос про
Federal Reserve System, yes, they
Федеральную резервную систему его да
wanted to kill Trump at the stage of the
Трампа хотели убить ещё на этапе
election campaign, that's what
предвыборной кампании вот это что в ухо
this shooter shot him in the ear, so I think
ему стрельнул этот стрелок вот я думаю
that now, let's say, Trump is a
что сейчас его ну скажем Трамп он волк
lone wolf, you understand, he is trying to
одиночка понимаешь он же пробует там
disband the FBI, the CIA, he has no team, that
распустить ФБР ЦРУ у него нет команды то
is, he does not have a deep state
есть у него нету глубинного государства
that will protect him  and the Morgans and the
которое будет его защищать а Морганы и
Rockefellers, they uh, built parallel
Рокфелеры они ээ строили параллельные
structures, yes, you understand that the entire FBI,
структуры да ты же понимаешь что всё ФБР
this CIA, they are simply
Ф вот это ЦРУ они пронизаны просто
permeated with these agents, uh, let's
пронизанными вот этими агентами ээ
say, of the world behind the scenes, and that's why
скажем мировой закулисы и поэтому вот
maybe you know the Bilderberg Club,
может знаешь Бильдербержский клуб
oh, there aren't any clubs there, but they, they
ой там каких-то клубов нету да они же
created the concept of the golden
они же сделали концепцию золотого
billion, you see, they created
миллиарда понимаешь это же они сделали
the concept of the golden billion, and Trump, uh, you think
концепцию золотого миллиарда и Трамп ээ
that Trump, he kind of wants to
ты вот думаешь что Трамп он как бы хочет
break the Federal Reserve System, but do you really think that in
сломать ФРС но неужели ты думаешь что в
that pseudo-democracy that is the USA, yes,
той псевдодемократии которая есть США да
these powers that be would allow
вот эти сильный мир сего допустили бы
him to run in the elections?
его к выборам
I think there are globalists there who,
я думаю
in short,
которые вот короче
well, now the globalists are fighting, and
ну сейчас сражаются глобалисты и
who,
и кто
well, the globalists are these Obama Democrats,
ну глобалисты - это эти демократы Обамы
they are conservatives, you
они консерваторы
could say so, and now there is a
вот можно сказать так и вот сейчас идёт
confrontation going on, I think Trump has a
противостояние я думаю у Трампа есть
chance, his
шанс вот это всё у него у него сейчас
task now is to destroy all of this, simply destroy, and how it
задача разрушить просто разрушить а как
was to the ground, we will
вот как было до основания мы
destroy it to the ground, and then not, this is what the communists
разрушим а потом не это коммунисты это
said, the whole world to the ground, that's
говорили весь мир до основания вот
about the same thing  we will destroy the whole world to its
примерно то же самое весь мир до
foundations and then we will
основания мы разрушим а потом будем
build it up and then how it will turn out but he
строить потом уже как получится но он
gives out such things that it is completely incomprehensible on We I
такое выдаёт что вообще непонятно на Мы
think you also wake up there and
я думаю вы тоже там просыпаетесь да и
google what Trump said today not me
гуглите что же сегодня заявил Трамп не я
look I understand I
смотри я я понимаю
understand that let's say uh what
я понимаю что скажем ээ то что делает
Trump is doing is all staged as if
Трамп - это всё срежиссированное как бы
uh speech real politics goes on behind
ээ выступление реальная политика идёт за
the scenes yes world look uh who is where
кулисами да мировая смотри ээ кто где
where is the world center of the Anglo-Saxons the
где находится мировой центр англосаксов
center of decision-making well there
центр принятия решений
is the Vatican there
ну есть Ватикан
are also some forces uh well in
есть ещё есть силы ээ какие-то ну в
Britain London yes still London
Британии Лондон да всё-таки Лондон как
whatever it is London and
бы там как бы там ни было Лондон и
look all here MI6 yes
смотри вся вот Ми6 да разведка
British intelligence who does it consist of from the
британская из кого она состоит из
London
лондонской
aristocracy that is the entire London
аристократии то есть вся лондонская
aristocracy it works in some
аристократия она работает в каких-то
special services that is they supervise there
спецслужбах то есть они курируют там
ordinary workers such are and all
рядовые работники такие есть а все вот
these lords snipers yes they all have
эти лор лорды срыперы да они все имеют
certain positions in MI6 and uh
определённые должности в Мишесть и ээ
Britain exactly yes it has an influence on
Британия именно да она имеет влияние на
world politics it was the British
мировую политику она же была британская
Empire in after the second yes after  During the Second
империя в после второй да после Второй
World War, different parts of it fell away
мировой войны от неё отвалились разные
and it simply made a decision: "We
части и она просто приняла решение: "Мы
will govern covertly, yes, why pay
будем управлять неявно да зачем платить
pensions to a billion Indians if you can
пенсии миллиарду индусов если можно
govern secretly, yes, not pay them anything, yes, but
управлять тайно да не платить им что-то
get everything you need from them, well,
да а получать от них всё что нужно ну
the empire is gone, there are no more
вот империи уже нету
forces, there are no more, but there is such a thing as the English, like
сил уже нету но есть такое англичан как
gadt, yes, yes, they very clearly take
гадт вот да да они они очень чётко берут
and, let's say, take control of entire
и скажем берут под контроль целые
states, entire states, and if you think that
государства целые и если ты думаешь что
America, it kind of freed itself from
Америка она как бы освободилась от
England, then the war for independence, the
Англии тогда война за независимость
proclamation of the United States, the
провозглашение Соединённых Штатов отцы
founding fathers, uh, if you look, on
основатели ээ если ты посмотришь то на
dollar bills there are
денежных купюрах доллара есть
certain Masonic
определённые масонские
signs and an eye and a pyramid, it's
знаки и и глаз и пирамида
true, everyone knows this, well, this is no longer such a thing, this is
правда это все знают ну это уже такое не
all clear because look, it
это всё чётко потому что смотри это так
was the same, yes, that America, yes, Great Britain
же было да что Америка да Великобритания
threw off the yoke of holding these
скинула с себя ээ ярмо удержания этих
territories with money, it
территорий деньгами она теперь не вклады
should not have invested in the
не должна была вкладываться в
infrastructure of the United States, but
инфраструктуру Соединённых Штатов да вот
you are already independent, yes, but in
вы же как бы уже независимые да но по
fact they remained completely dependent
факту они остались полностью зависимые
on the British Navy  rights that's all well that's all
от британского морского права вот и всё
they have left is
ну вот вот у них только и остаётся это
somewhere something
где-то что-то
but it was not for nothing that they
но они же не зря не зря с Евросоюза
announced Brexit with the European Union they
брексит объявили с Евросоюза они же
probably knew something yes and I'll tell you
наверное что-то знали да а я скажу
why I'll tell you because look
почему я скажу потому что смотри
the concept of Britain yes it is control of the seas
концепция Британии да это контроль морей
control of all the seas that is Britain
контроль всех морей то есть у Британии
is like a maritime power yes yes yes but in
она как морская держава да да да но в
the past well no they still
прошлом ну так нет так они до сих пор
they still dream of it they live by it
они до сих пор этим э мечтают они зиятся
they live by it and look if we
живут они этим живут и смотри если мы
look at during the Russian Empire
посмотрим в во время Российской империи
yes British holdings controlled the
да британские холдинги контролировали
ports during the time when the Soviet Union
порты во время когда Советский Союз
Lenin rose up and overthrew the imperial power
Ленин восстал да скинул имперскую власть
uh the British who supported Kolchak the
э англичане кого поддерживали колчака
White Guards the British landed them where
белогвардейцев англичане высадили их где
in Arkhangelsk on the North Sea in the ports
в Архангельске на Северном море в портах
they began the intervention was yes that is
они начали интервенция была да то есть
and now why did they do Brexit
и сейчас почему сделали они брексит
because in let's say Europe it is
потому что в скажем Европа она
continental Europe it grew out
континентальная Европа она выросла как
of land uh states yes that is
бы из сухопутных ээ государств да то
Britain it is more of a maritime
есть э Британия она более морская
power  and she had a conflict with Europe
держава и у неё стал конфликт с Европой
about control of the Baltic, control of the Black Sea
о контроле Балтики контроле Чёрного моря
and control of the Mediterranean, yes, in this
и контроле Средиземного да ээ в этом
regard they did not agree and that is why Britain
плане они не сошлись и поэтому Британия
did Brexit and went with Who
сделала брексит и пошла с Кто
controls the exit from the Mediterranean Sea
контролирует выход из Средиземного моря
to the Atlantic Ocean, I
в Атлантический океан
wonder why they
вот вот интересно почему они вообще
should do anything at all already Well, you saw, look, what
что-то должны уже Ну ты видел смотри что
is Gibraltar, look, the exit from the
такое Гибралтар смотри выход из
Mediterranean Sea to the Atlantic Ocean
Средиземного моря в Атлантический океан
passes through the Strait of Gibraltar, what is Gibraltar, it is a
проходит через Гибралтарский пролив что
small rock, a
такое Гибралтар это маленькая скала
small rock that belongs to
маленькая скала которая принадлежит
Britain, that is, Gibraltar, yes, it is
Британии то есть Гибралтар да
completely subordinate to the queen, uh, in
подчиняется полностью королев ээ вот в
London, that is, a rock on a piece of Spain, there is a
Лондоне то есть скала на кусочке Испании
rock there is a small airfield
стоит скала там маленький аэродромчик
that only fits in and that's it and this rock
только вмещается и всё и эта скала
controls the entire passage between Africa and
контролирует весь проход между Африкой и
Europe, the Strait of Gibraltar, the sea,
Европой гибралтарский пролив моря вот
just imagine, little
вот представляете себе вот маленькая
England and something there and everywhere, that's all
Англия и что-то там и везде вот вот всё
they have these imperial ambitions left,
у них вот эти имперские амбиции остались
although in general there is nothing
хотя вообще от от имперскости уже ничего
left of imperialism, well, wait, they still have a
не осталось ну подожди у них до сих пор
king and  queen yes they are still the
король есть и королева да они до сих пор
british empire essentially well
британская империя по сути
how do they call it they are called
ну как они же называ они же называются
Great Britн Great Britain we
Great Britн Великая Британия мы же
watched there how this
смотрели там как это
something there their like this
этот что-то там ихней как вот это
which is the eldest how do they have what is his name
которая там старший как у них как его
there Chani what is his name well this is with the
там чани как его там звать ну вот это с
actress he is something there and then they
актрисой он там что-то и потом они
left refused the crown this is this well
уехали отказались от короны это вот это
this is already some kind of split in the empire
ну это уже раскол какой-то в империи
when to say all these imperial people don't
когда сказати все вот эти имперские не
like
нравятся
and what is Milton or what is her name I do
и по как же Милтон или как её там звать
n't know well you are watching there well this is the
не знаю ну вы же там следите ну вот это
eldest son the eldest who is red-haired
вот старший сын старший который рыжий
harrykto Harry yes Harry Harry yes he
гарикто Гарри да гарри гарри да он вот
got married and and they started having friction there this
это женился и а у них там тёрки начались
and they left for America
вот это и они там уехали в Америку они ж
these British they are cunning they seem to
вот эти британцы они хитрые они вроде
support Christianity yes as if
типа поддерживают христианство да как бы
they are Christians yes but they have
они вроде христиане да но у них
these druidic
распространены вот эти друидические
Celtic beliefs yes they unofficially
кельские верования да они неофициально
perform these rituals this prince
проводят вот эти обряды вот этот принц
Harry yes the bearded one he is Why
Гарри да бородатый он же Почему
red beards are a Celtic theme yes being
рыжебороды это кельская тема да быть
red beards
рыжебородами
yes Scottish something there and so the
да шотландское что-то там и так
Scots are also Celts yes they are
шотландцы - это тоже кельты да это же
Celts and they have this fetish
кельты вот и у них есть вот этот фетиш
even if the beard is not red they
даже если борода не рыжая они
dye it red that's how they hold
подкрашивают в рыжую так они проводят
why Stonehenge look here somewhere
почему Стоунхнж вот смотри у нас где-то
yes on the territory of Russia where some
да на территории там России где какая-то
old pagan temple was built there a
староя языческая капи там построили
church was built why there is still no church on Stonehenge
церковь почему на Стоунхендже до сих пор
because the British crown
церковь потому что британская корона
considers Stonehenge its sacred
считает Стоунхендж своим священным
place they hold their
местом они проводят там свои
rituals there you knew if you read there was such a
обряды ты знал если почитай был такой
Peter Jackson in Britain the author of the
Питер Джексон в Британии автор
whistleblower he was this how is it a
разоблачитель он был этим как оно
writer by the way Stonehenge is
писателем таким кстати Стоунхндж - это
Yes it is generally a wonder of the world of some kind yes and
Да это вообще чудо света какого-то да и
he look him he was found last year
он смотри его его его в прошлом году
as if dead found dead under
нашли как бы мёртвым нашли мёртвым при
mysterious circumstances and he was just
загадочных обстоятельствах а он как раз
writing about the fact that the royal family
писал о том что королевская семья
holds these and the aristocracy
проводит вот эти и аристократия
they are formally Christians yes it seems
они формально есть христианами да вроде
and they come to church on Easter, yes,
как и приходят там в церковь на Пасху да
but they really support all these old
но реально поддерживают все эти старые
Druidic practices, they support
друидические практики поддерживают
Stonehenge, they made Stonehenge
Стоунхендж сделали из Стоунхенджа чуть
almost a Mecca, that everyone comes there, in
ли не Мекку что туда приезжают все по
fact, they worship these idols,
сути они поклоняются вот этим идолам
like, well, people come, Stone sect,
типа ну люди приезжают Стоун секта секта
some kind of sect, yes, yes, and there and immediately they start,
какая-то да да да и там и сразу начинают
even in Russia, there in Ukraine, about
там уже даже в России там в Украине о
Stonehenge, wow, like they start to spin
Стоунхндж вау типа начинают раскручивать
this topic, so that and by the way, this
эту тему вот так что и кстати вот этот
Halloween, Halloween, where did it come from, it’s
Хэллоуин Хэллоуин откуда ж пошёл это ж
also Celtic, these Druidic
тоже кельские вот эти друидические
beliefs, yes, the worship of the dead, it
верования да поклонение мёртвым оно
came from Britain to America,
пришло из Британии в Америку
spread in Europe, and now it has reached
распространилось в Европе и теперь дошло
us in the Slavic states, we
к нам в славянских государствах у нас
never put candles in pumpkins, I don’t
никогда в тыкву свечки не ставили я не
remember Prince Vladimir celebrating
помню чтобы князь Владимир да праздновал
Halloween, it’s completely wild, yes, and now our
Хэллоуин это вообще дико да да и сейчас
children, our children, you know, our
дети у нас дети понимаешь наши
Slavic children take this pumpkin, cut it out,
славянские дети берут эту тыкву вырезают
and put a
и ставят туда
candle in it, what can they do, what can they graft,
свечу что они могут какие могут привить
why is this done, you know, wow, you’re
для чего это делается понимаешь ух ты
nothing special, but you used to be in Ukraine
ничего себе а вы же раньше же в Украине
well they supported all these
ну поддерживали это все вот эти вот
movements yes well I see something not I
движения да ну я смотрю что-то не Я
see your rhetoric is changing so easily
смотрю у вас риторика так просто
with the arrival of Trump when he said
меняется с приходом Трампа когда он вот
this that it turns out that there is a
этозал что оказывае оказывается что есть
man and a woman and
мужчина и женщина и
still a man and a
всё-таки мужчина и
woman I still explain look I have
женщина я ещё объясняю смотри я свою
never changed my point of view I just for
точку зрения никогда не менял я просто
example publicly You don't record me
например публично Ты не записываешь меня
at least no no no because I can't
хотя бы не не не потому что я не могу в
go out in Ukraine and tell I know you
Украине выйти и рассказывать я знаю вы
record You I know don't record no don't
запи Вы Я знаю не записывай не не
record it yes yes well they ask I know the
записывай её да да ну просят я знаю
channel Andrey Popik is like that yes yes that's how it
канал Андрей Попик такой да да то
turns out and look and with these pumpkins you
получается и смотри и с этими тыквами
know you know through whom I'm not even
знаешь знаешь через кого я даже не
against if this conversation you know for
против если этот разговор знаешь для
whom they introduced through whom they introduced
кого внедрили через кого внедряли вот
these pumpkins Halloweens through
эти тыквы Хэллоуины через школы
English language schools look at you in
английского языка посмотри у вас в
Russia take a closer look at all the English
России присмотрись все школы английского
language schools yes in the fall they do the
языка да они осенью делают тему
Halloween theme like English culture
Хэллоуин как бы английская культура
American culture and everything yes that is
американская культура и всё да то есть
first they promoted Santa Claus with
сначала нам продвинули Санта-Клауса с
Co-Cola to us through commerce yes it's just
Ко-колой через коммерцию да это просто
com commerce just look how I
ко коммерция просто смотрите как мне
like how everything is with you well that's how it
нравится как у вас всё ну это ж так и
was like with you how  you then have these yes well
было как вас как у вас потом вот эти да
and genders and everything is fine yes well
ну и гендеры и всё нормально же да ну
this is all wild for the Slavs we don't need this
это всё дико славянам нам это не надо
right of course not that's it for us for
правильно конечно нет вот вот у нас у
us and the Slavs the only case was
нас и у славян единственный случай был
when there were rulers this is Askold Idir
когда были правители это Аскольт Идир
princes maybe you remember princes Askold Idir the
князья может помнишь князья Аскольз Идир
first yes same-sex rulers of Rus' yes and
первые да однополые правители Руси да а
so it turns out well let's say we Slavs don't need
так получается ну скажем нам славянам не
we need to reproduce we Slavs
надо нам надо размножаться нам славянам
need by the way how old are you how many
надо кстати сколько у тебя лет сколько у
children do you have I have
тебя детей
two and how old are you well
у меня двое а сколько тебе лет
over 40 that is how do you have over 40 years and
ну за 40 то есть как у тебя за 40 лет а
only two children a Tajik already has six that's why
детей только двое у таджика уже шестеро
they reproduce that's what I
вот они размножаются вот вот я об этом и
wanted to talk about that we Slavs have few
хотел поговорить что у нас славян мало
children born and Tajiks they have
детей рождается а у таджиков у них по
five or six so what's the problem with
пять по шесть так а в чём проблема у
you that already 40 the maternity ward doesn't work I
тебя что уже 40 рожалка не работает не
can't understand why
могу понять почему так
not everything is like that well we reproduced
не всё ну мы так вот воспроизвели сами
ourselves that's how to stop you from giving birth because
себя что мешает тебе роди потому что
not because children need to be
потому что не потому что детям надо
educated they need to be given well they need you
образование отдать надо им ну их надо
understand and how many children do you have
вот вот понимаешь а у тебя сколько детей
Andrey four
Андрей четверо
oh yeah well done yeah  Well done and now the fifth one is
о да молодец да молодец и сейчас пятый
already hatching
уже вот вынашиваем
Well done I'm proud of you Well I'm just you
молодец горжусь тобой ну я только ты вот
please don't need this Bandera propaganda so that we have to
пропаганду пожалуйста не надо чтоб с
live with the Russians we are Slavs we are Slavs well
русскими надо жить мы славяне мы так мы
Bandera was also a Slav how come
славяне ну Бандера тоже славянин был как
he wasn't Austro-Hungarian Well how come he is a
как не он там Австровенграр ну как он
Slav
славянин
no no no we will have to live with the Russians anyway
нене не надо с русскими всё равно
no need to get ready Yes we
придётся жить не надо настраиваться да
look we we think the
мы смотри мы мы считаем всё равно
war will end anyway someday Yes we
когда-нибудь война закончится да мы
consider the Russians to be brothers just
считаем русских братьями просто
lost they betrayed the SA because
заблудшими они предали СА потому что
when we also yours also in the fact that
когда мы также ваш также де в том что
when Genghis Khan yes first
когда Чингисхан да захватил Русь сначала
he burned Moscow then captured Kyiv yes a
он сжёг Москву потом захватил Киев да
year later eh Kyiv was recaptured from Genghis Khan after 80 years
через год ээ Киев через 80 лет отбили от
and Moscow remained for 300 years and
Чингисхана а Москва осталась 300 лет и
why do you now have
вы сейчас почему у вас сейчас вот эти
all these swords Poles there so the Poles are also
все мече поляки там так поляки тоже
Slavs Yes we are Slavs we would be with the Slavs
славяне да мы славяне бы мы со славянами
they are for the Western
они за западные
Slavs yes but you were under the Tatar-Mongols
славя да но вы были под татаро-монголами
that is look now  who do you have
то есть смотри сейчас кто у вас у вас
Russia now you have Russia not a Slavic
Россия теперь у вас Россия не славянское
state you have it Chechen there
государство у вас оно чеченское там
Tatar Kalmyk everything for example I
татарское калмыцкое всё вот например
agree that for example you are against a Chechen
согласен что ты например против чеченца
nothing US federation we have a federation now
ничего не сш федерация у нас сейчас
not us here in Kuban I live in Kuban in
не мы вот на Кубане я живу на Кубане на
Krasnodar we have well there are a lot of Armenians there
в Краснодаре у нас ну армяне там много
yes there there already look agree I
там да там там уже смотри согласись я
saw I saw that Armenians are already in Kuban
видел я видел что армян уже на Кубани
10% Russians all 10% already Armenians look
10% русские все 10% уже армян смотри
Dagestanis are settling Kuban more yes
дагестанцы заселяют Кубане больше да
more in Sochi there there yes that is it
больше в Сочи там туда да то есть
turns out they are displacing they hold all the business the
получается они вытесня они весь бизнес
whole coast hold who is not
держат всё побережье держат кто не
Russian true
русские правда
they trade more if you go to
они торгуют больше если зайдёшь в
some Kromnitsa Kromnitsa there are some
какую-нибудь кромницу кромницу там
battalions something there agree that all the
придбаты чтось там согласись что весь
business all the business is held yes not Russian
бизнес весь бизнес держат да не русские
true in Krasnodar Krai
правда в Краснодарском крае
well it depends on what kind of business well it is not them so they
ну как смотря какой бизнес ну такой не
trade in the bazaars there something like that that is
они так на базарах торгуют там что-то
look trade they
такое то есть вот смотри торговля они
like to trade trade yes that is they
любят торговать торговать да то есть они
trade  shopping centers and so on and so
торговля торговые центры также и так
forth that is all under the
дальше то есть это всё под
Azerbaijanis, Armenians, Chechens yes that
азербайджанцами армянами чеченнами да то
is it turns out that Russians are being economically
есть получается русских экономически
displaced some time ago and even
вытесняют когда-то раньше да ещё даже
under the Soviet Union Russian business is doing
при советском русский бизнес делают
serious business what kind of well here is an
серьёзный бизнес какой какой ну вот
enterprise a large enterprise what
предприятие крупное предприятие какое
name an enterprise which is Russian production production production
назови предприятие которое русски
name well
назови
here I work I work at an
ну вот я работаю я работаю на
enterprise we manufacture
предприятии мы изготавливаем
metal structures we have Russians we all
металлоконструкции у нас русские все
cooperate with Russians and customers here all
сотрудничаем с русскими и заказчики вот
come Russians all and who is this for
все приезжают русские всё а кто это
example the owner the owner the
например собственник собственник
owner the director our no not the director
собственник директор наш не не директор
- this is the one who was appointed director but there
- это тот кого поставили директором а
is an owner look there is an owner
есть собственник смотри есть собственник
not he he is he is from the very bottom
не он он и есть он от самого самых низов
he what is his Russian surname
он как его у него русская фамилия
elisako
елисако
it is already Ukrainian well as if yes
это уже украинска ну как бы да
Ukrainian yes yes everything you see I am saying
украинская да да всё видишь я же говорю
not Russian here look here recently with
не русская вот вот смотри вот недавно с
e such a verse verse read here listen to
э такой вирш вирш прочитал вот послушай
me carefully yeah the sun beam was dying
меня внимательно угу солнце луч умирал
on the broken concrete and it was watched from
на разбитом бетоне и за ним наблюдали с
different sides Ukrainian soldier Ivanov
разных сторон украинский солдат Иванов
Anatoly and  Russian soldier Prokopenko
Анатолий и российский солдат Прокопенко
Anton
Антон
yes very much yes that's all that's what I'm saying
да сильно да вот всё вот я же говорю
but Budanov Syrskikh well why
но Буданов Сырских ну ну что всё
mix everything up we are very close if I
поперемеш мы с вами очень близки если
remember was cool too I also heard
вспомню был классный тоже у тоже слышал
such a verse damn now now I remember
такой стих блин сейчас сейчас вспомню
somehow uh but
как-то ээ а вот
at dawn dawn No now now
на на рассвете заря Нет сейчас сейчас
now how it was
сейчас как там
and at sunset oh yes uh at
было а на закате во да
sunset by the
ээ на закате у
river at sunset by the river uh the
речки на закате у речки
sun was setting and oh at sunset by the river
ээ солнце сади а во на закате у речки
the sun was setting
солнце садилось
his
свою
here he
тут
accepted accepted he uh a
принял принял же он
guy from Rostov Prokhorov Sanya in the
ээ парень с Ростова Прохоров Саня в
head Ukrainian drone that's how it was
бошку украинс дрон вот так было
yes such a tragic story
да такая трагическая история
well drones hit the head here and
ну вот в бошку попадают дроны и туда и
here well tragedy for them what hits them and
сюда ну трагедия им что им попадает а
mothers wives children cry understood and what do you
матеря жёны дети плачут понял а как ты
think why Russia then kills
считаешь зачем Россия тогда убивает
Slavs with itself with Russian and Ukrainian
славян собой с российской и с украинской
question well no not with pleasure
вопрос ну вот не не с удовольствием
soldiers kill
солдаты убивают
Slavs there are well there are orders there is an order of a soldier the
славян есть ну есть приказы есть приказ
soldier has what well there is an order it
солда у солдата что ну есть приказ вот
must be carried out I'll tell you I'll tell you
надо его исполнять я вам я вам скажу вот
unlike you by the way nobody  I
в отличие от вас кстати никто я вот
see here that no one is happy about the
здесь вот вижу никто не радуется ну
deaths of Ukrainians, and even more so if
смертям украинцев и тем более и если там
someone peaceful is guiding there, it dies, it is a
кто-то мирный гидит это гибнет это это
tragedy, but I look at yours, I just
трагедия ну а я смотрю вот ваши просто я
know Ukrainian, I just studied it, I know Ukrainian
украинский знаю ну просто изучил я знаю
inside and out, yeah, and I look at
украинский от и до угу вот и я смотрю
your news and just, well, you have, like, well, to be
ваши новости и просто ну у вас как бы ну
honest, well, especially
честно говоря просто ну вот особенно
Sternenko, I like to listen to him,
Стерненко вот я вот люблю послушать что
he is such a Russophobe - it's just awful,
уже он такой русофоб - это просто ужас
and he says that our Russophobia is
и он говорит что наша русофоби
insufficient, insufficient, yes, enough, yes, ah, ah, and
недостатне недостатне да достатня да а а
how, and when will it be enough, well,
а а как а когда будет достатне ну ну
enough, there is another Russophobe, Dmitry
достатня есть ещё один русофоб Дмитрий
Korchinsky, he came up with the formula that peace is
Корчинский он вывел формулу что мир -
not ots - it is not the absence of war,
это не отсу - это не отсутствие войны
peace is the absence of Moscow, but if
мир - это отсутствие Москвы вот если
Moscow is absent, our
будет отсутствовать Москва наша
Russophobia will be enough,
русофобия будет достатня
not Moscow, it was, is and will be, and we would like
не Москва она была есть и будет и нам
Kyiv to be, to live and
хотело бы чтобы Киев был вот жил и
prosper, well, it's just, well, it was possible, well, to
процветал ну просто ну можно же было ну
end this war, well, to come to an agreement,
закончить эту войну ну договориться
somehow, it's very simple, we agree,
как-то так очень просто договариваемся
you withdraw your troops from Ukraine and that's it,
вы выводите войска из Украины и всё
stop the war, that's it  just agree
остановили войну всё просто договориться
what's the problem well it depends what is
что в чём проблема ну смотря смотря что
considered already the territory of Ukraine here
считать уже территорией Украины тут же
all the borders of the ninety-first year
всё границы девяносто первого года
legal territory of Ukraine why look come on come on
законная территория Украины зачем смотри
really look do you
давай давай давай реально смотри вам
really need territories or do you need
реально нужны территории или вам нужен
peace if you need peace exactly peace that's all
мир если вам нужен мир именно мир всё
if you have peace withdraw the territories give
если вам мир выведите территории отдайте
us uh Belgorod region Kursk
нам ээ Белгородскую область Курскую
Voronezh and Krasnodar region
Воронежскую и Краснодарский край
Rostov region and that's all and there will be peace
Ростовскую область ещё и всё и будет мир
yeah and what will you do with
ага а что вы будете делать с
Krasnodar region well here I will conduct
Краснодарским краем ну вот я будем
Ukrainization
украинизацию проводить
well and And why do we need it wait stop
ну и А нам она зачем подожди стоп ещё
again then you need peace and what can you offer us
раз то вам мир нужен а что вы нам можете
wait so what do you have to offer
предложить подожди так причём вам
you you will be told like you
предложить вас вы вам скажут типа вы
go there to the territory for example
идите там на территорию например
Stavropol region you will leave yourself if you
Ставропольского края вы себе уедете если
don't want to live under Ukraine what's the
не захотите жить под Украиной в чём
problem what can Ukraine give us we are
проблема что Украина нам может дать мы
not obliged to offer you anything we will
вам ничего не обязаны предлагать мы
take the territories for ourselves do you want peace for
заберём территории себе вы хотите мир
the sake of peace I asked do you need
ради мира я же спросил вам нужны
territories or peace you say: "Peace" well
территории или мир вы говорите: "Мир" ну
that's it get out of Crimea Donetsk
так всё выходите из Крыма Донецка
Lugansk yes get out of Kursk region
Луганска да выходите из Курской области
Belgorod Bryansk  Rostov
Белгородской Брянской Ростовской
Voronezh and Krasnodar regions and all
Воронежской и Краснодарского края и всё
who do not agree to live under Ukraine
кто не согласен жить под Украиной
leave for example to the Altai region
уезжает например в Алтайский край
Vladivostok there is Kolyma in short well what is the
Владивосток есть Колыма короче ну в чём
problem is clear clear clear and we
проблема понятно понятно понятно а мы
let's say stop stop then that
вот допустим вот стоп стоп то то то вам
means you need territories and not peace true
значит нужны территории а не мир правда
I'm on Nenene we can offer residents of
я по Ненене мы можем предложить жителям
Zaporozhye and Kherson that gasoline
в Запорожской и Херсонской что бензин
will be
будет
shi Let's agree let's have salaries
ши Давай договори давай зарплаты
higher salaries more pensions gasoline
зарплаты выше э пенсии больше бензин
cheaper gas cheaper and there just won't be a war
дешевле газ дешевле а и просто войны не
everything will be quiet and now look yes
будет всё будет тихо а теперь смотри да
explain I understood yes
у объясня я понял
early response early response
да до досрочный ответ досрочный ответ
look what what you we Ukrainians don't need
смотри что что вы нам украинцам не нужен
peace we need territories yes your
мир нам нужны территории да ваши
territories including yes you need peace
территории в том числе да вам нужен мир
so you can offer I suggest
так вот предложить вы можете я предлагаю
look compromise we don't need peace but we
смотри компромисс нам не нужен мир но
need territories we are more important territories you do
нужны территории нам важнее территории
n't care about territories you care about peace
вам не важны территории вам важен мир
so we can all agree you give us
так всё мы можем сойтись вы отдаёте нам
part of your territories
часть территорий своих
Kuban Krasnodar there this well there
кубань Краснодар там вот это ну там
Rostov and so on all this yes and we
Ростов и так дальше всё это да и мы
make peace you get what you
заключаем мир вы получаете то что вы
wanted peace we get what we
хотели мир мы получаем то что мы
get nonsense wait Top  Well, you
получаем бред подожди Топ ну ты же
say that you said in your own words
говоришь что ты же сказал своими словами
that territories are not important to you,
что вам территории не важны вам важен
peace is important to you, but I say the opposite, territories are important to us,
мир а я говорю наоборот нам важны
peace is not important to us, well, here's a
территории нам мир не важен ну вот
compromise, we get territories, you get
компромисс мы получаем территории вы
peace, everyone got what they
получаете мир всё каждый получил то что
wanted, what's the problem, that's how it is with us, we have
хотел в чём проблема так у нас у нас и
peace on the territory of Russia, peace no, no,
так мир на территории России мир нет нет
you live, that's how you know, well, Andrey,
вами живте это это как знаешь ну Андрей
it's like a mosquito bitten, no, look, no, that is, you have a
это как вот комару укусило не ну смотри
war, your
не то есть есть у вас есть война ваши
people are dying, dying, your people, that means it's not peace, everyone is dying,
люди умирают умирают умирают ваши люди
and ours, yours is a
значит не мир всё умирают да и наши ваши
tragedy, new, that means it's not peace, so if
это трагедия новы значит не мир так если
you want peace, look, go beyond the
вы хотите мира смотрите уйдите за Урал у
Urals, we have two, or go beyond the Urals, yes, we
нас есть два либо уходит за Урал да мы
take this, the 300 km buffer zone
забираем вот это буферную зону 300 км
around Ukraine, and
вокруг Украины а до Урала забирают
peacekeeping troops are being taken up to the Urals, he looks,
миротворческие войска водятся он смотри
Andrey, you're far from a stupid
Андрей ты же вот ну ты далеко не глупый
person, I watched your videos, yes,
человек я же ну смотрел твои ролики да
very much, yes, well, tell
очень да ну вот скажи вот только честно
me, can you honestly just tell me, right
мне можешь только честно сказать вот
now, at the moment, what do
сейчас на данный момент что вот сейчас
you think about this situation,
вот вот эта ситуация как ты думаешь
could we agree on the
вот можно было вот договориться на
Minsk agreements, that's how it is
Минских соглашениях вот чтобы вот этого
all this on Minsk on Minsk it say
всего на Минских на Минских это
say simply and
говори скажи просто и
disperse Minsk disperse 100% we
разойдись Мински разойдись 100% мы же
signed the Minsk agreements and in
подписали Минские соглашения и вы через
3 days you violated them captured Debaltseve
3 дня их нарушили захватили Дебальцева
look the Minsk agreements were signed on
посмотри Минские соглашения подписаны 12
February 12 yes you captured Debaltseve on the
февраля да Дебальцева вы захватили
fifteenth
пятнадцатого
look in the Minsk agreements look in the
посмотри в Минских соглашени смотри в
Minsk agreements there is a clear
минских соглашениях есть чётко
ceasefire withdrawal of foreign troops
прекращение огня вывод иностранных войск
yes Russian yes so look well I am
да российски да так смотри ну я тебе
telling you more globally all this I understand
более глобально говорю это всё я понимаю
that look we signed the Minsk
что смотри мы подписали Минские
agreements on February 12 shook hands there
соглашения 12 февраля пожали руки там
everything yes in the Minsk agreements there was a
все да в Минских соглашениях было
ceasefire and withdrawal of foreign and
остановка огня и вывод иностранных и
armed formations that is Russia
вооружённых формирований то есть Россия
should have withdrawn Russia immediately
должна была вывести россия сразу же
violated Russia deceived us we signed the
наруши россия обманула нас мы подписали
Minsk agreements stopped the fire and
Минские соглашения остановили огонь а
Russia went and launched an offensive on
Россия взяла и сделала наступление на
Debaltseve and captured Debaltseve
Дебальцева и захватила Дебальцева
look Debaltseve was captured on February 15
посмотри Дебальцево захвачено 15 февраля
Minsk agreements on the twelfth how do you
Минские соглашение двенадцатого как ты
explain this
это объяснишь
look I understand that there were well, well-
смотри я понимаю что были вот ну
groomed, how is it, Russian-
налаштованный как это по-русски
minded friend, you have already begun to forget
настроенный друг ты уже стал забывать
Russian,
русский язык
yes I know Ukraine, I watched so much of your
да я знаю Украи я столько из ваших
news today, here it is, look, look,
новостей сегодня посмотрел вот она у
Russia has not yet given us the
смотри смотри россия ещё нам не отдала
Krasnodar region, but you have already
Краснодарский край но ты уже русский
begun to forget Russian, well done,
язык начал забывать молодец
no I know Ukrainian, explain well,
не я знаю украинские объясни хорошо
explain to me how it happened that
объясни мне как так получилось что
Ukraine signed the Minsk
Украина подписала Минские
agreements, a ceasefire, everything, and
соглашения прекращение огня всё а через
three days later Russia captured Dybaltseve, how did it
3 дня Россия захватила Дыбальцево как
happen
так получилось
because there were your nationalist battalions and
потому что были вот ваши нацбатальоны и
our volunteers, yes they are there, and the DPR people,
наши добровольцы да они там и и днровцы
and they also joined in, and there were no
и там подтянулись ещё да и там уже не
agreements, you understand, so stop, stop,
договоров было понимаешь так стоп стоп
you say it turns out that Ukraine is a
ты говоришь то получается Украина
political process at the top, and people, do
политический процесс идёт вверху а люди
I understand correctly that I
я правильно понимаю что Я правильно
understand correctly that Ukraine signed the Minsk
понимаю что Украина подписала Минские
agreements and violated them, not it, yes,
соглашения и нарушила их не она
someone violated them, show me again,
нарушали кто-нибудь кни ещё раз покажи
no, look, on February 12, 2015, the
нет смотри 12 февраля 2015 года
Minsk agreements were signed, no,
подписаны Минские соглашения был нет
three days later Debaltseve was captured by
через 3 дня было захвачено Дебальцево
Russia, yes, how did it happen  so it was
России да как так получилось значит
n't Ukraine that violated it was Russia that violated it
нарушила не Украина нарушила Россия
turns out Debaltseve not Debaltseve it's all not
получается дебальцева не Дебальцева это
all this people came to us and
всё не это всё это у нас приезжали люди
told us yes once again look
рассказывали да ещё раз ещё раз смотри
if there ka again why didn't Russia
если там ка ещё раз почему Россия не
give Debaltseve back to Ukraine I have do you
отдала Дебальцева назад Украину у меня
want me to show you a video no I don't need a video
есть хочешь я тебе видео покажу нет не
you explain No you're convinced No I don't
надо мне видео ты объяс Нет ты убе Нет
need a video you explain to me you
мне не нужно видео ты мне объясни ты
opened your mouth about the Minsk agreements that it was
открыл рот про Минские соглашения что
possible to agree I'm telling you we
можно было договориться я же говорю мы
agreed yes we agreed on the
же договорились да мы пошли на те
conditions that let's stop so that people
условия что давайте остановим чтобы люди
don't die yes we'll stop right now we're
не гибли да остановим вот сейчас прямо
stopping the fighting and no we
останавливаем боевые действия и нет
drew demarcation lines even and
прочертили линии разграничения даже и
so on and so on 3 days later Russia captured
так дальше через 3 дня Россия захватила
Debaltseve how did it happen so
Дебальцева как получилось так
what does it mean Russia captured Debaltseve
что ж значит Россия захватила Дебальцева
there
там со стороны России
were volunteers on the Russian side look again Russia
были добровольцы ещё раз смотри Россия
signed the Minsk agreements Russia
подписала Минские соглашения россия их
signed them Russia had to
подписала россия должна была их
implement them everything was from below once again
исполнять всего было и снизу ещё раз
Russia from below not from below it doesn't matter if
Россия снизу не снизу да неважно если
Russia came from below and said: "Well,
снизу пришла Россия сказала: "Так а ну
move back according to the Minsk agreements
отодвиньтесь по Минским соглашениям
Debaltseve - this is Ukraine, there is a
дебальцева - это Украина есть линия
demarcation line" why didn't she give it
разграничения" почему она не дала
yes no one controlled anything there you
да там никто ничего не контролировал
see it was necessary there Wait if you did
понимаешь там надо было Подожди если вы
n't control anything how could you
ничего не контролировали как вы могли
sign the Minsk agreements if you did
подписать Минские соглашения если вы
n't control anything again and
ничего не контролировали ещё раз так и
yours nothing wait again so what
ваши ничего подожди ещё раз так в чём
then stop if you say that Russia
тогда стоп если ты говоришь что Россия
signed the Minsk agreements and now you
подписала Минские соглашения а теперь
say that Russia didn't
говоришь что Россия ничего не
control anything how did it sign what it did
контролировала как она подписывала то
n't control
что не контролировала
signed agreements on the conclusion yes well that
подписали договорённости о заключении да
is Russia will agree with
ну то есть Россия договорится
represent no there no there wasn't
с представите нет там нет там не было
that Russia will agree there was clearly yes
что Россия договорится там чётко было да
that Russia takes on the responsibilities of
что Россия берёт на себя обязанности
Ukraine Russia wasn't such that it
Украины россия не было такого что она
signed an agreement with someone it was
подписывалась договориться с кем-то было
clear the withdrawal of foreign troops with
чётко вывод иностранных с
representatives of the DLNR LNR like as if No there wasn't such a thing
представителями ДЛНР ЛНР типа как бы Нет
in the Minsk
не было не было такого в Минске
agreements that Russia should
соглашений что Россия должна
agree there was a clear clause the withdrawal of
договориться был чёткий пункт вывод
foreign troops from Ukraine yes there was
иностранных войск из Украины да было
influence there was influence and no look in the
влияние было влияние и нет смотри в
Minsk agreements look in the Minsk
Минских соглашениях смотри в Минских
agreements there was a clear clause the withdrawal of
соглашениях был чёткий пункт вывод
foreign armed formations
иностранных вооружённых формирований с
why didn't Russia
территории Украины почему Россия не
withdraw its armed formations from the territory of Ukraine
вывела свои вооружённые формирования
because there were volunteers there
потому что там добровольцы шли
volunteers again again again
добровольцы ещё раз ещё
why if there were volunteers there yes
Ещё раз почему если там были добровольцы
only why was there a point on the withdrawal of
да только то почему было пункт вывод
foreign military formations
иностранных военных формирований
where are the foreign ones in the Minsk
это где ну иностранны в минских
agreements yes
соглашениях да
something like that wasn't there look at the Minsk
что-то такого не было посмотри Минские
agreements yes open open the withdrawal of
соглашения да открой открой вывод
foreign and
иностранных и
A yes well what point well now I'll say
А да ну а какой пункт ну сейчас я скажу
come on foreign come on now well
давай иностранный давай сейчас ну
read I'll read something about this now I do
прочитай я сейчас по этом что-то я
n't remember something like that now we'll open it for you right
такого не помню сейчас мы тебе прямо
here right on the OSCE website oh you have a
откроем вот прямо на сайте ОБС о у тебя
trident right on this and where can I
трезубец прямо на этом а где такое
buy that I
купить
also have that oh look look do you want me to
я тоже такое о смотри смотри хочешь я
show you look so look look what I have look
тебе покажу вот смотри так
yes
смотри смотри что у меня есть смотри да
look super super yes and this and
смотри супер супер да и вот это и вот
this look Mindozhey look how look how it
это смотри Миндожей смотри как смотри
looks together Andryu
как вместе смотрится Андрю
sorry yes in short here's the first point to
сори да короче вот первый пункт
ensure an immediate bilateral
обеспечить незамедлительное двустороннее
cessation of the use of weapons Russia
прекращение применения оружия Россия
violated yes and uh here's point number 10 to
нарушила да и ээ вот пункт номер 10
withdraw  illegal armed
вывести незаконные вооружённые
formations military equipment as well as
формирования военную технику а также
fighters and mercenaries from the territory of
боевиков и наёмников с территории
Ukraine Russia did not drive out Russia did not howl
Украины россия не выбила россия не выла
I and I understood I understood what you are talking about yes because a
я а я понял я понял о чём речь да потому
bunch of volunteers rushed to defend well
ломанулись куча добровольцев защищать ну
brothers from Donbass because well yes and
братьев с Донбасса потому что ну да и
Russia had to just like that by the scruff of the neck
Россия должна была так вот за шкирку их
pull them all out don't bother we
всех повыдёргивать всё не лезьте мы
will finish the conversation look okay let's
будем договаривать смотри да ладно
go volunteers look well here is what kind of
поехали добровольцы смотри ну вот какую
military equipment should have been withdrawn from the
военную технику должны были вывести с
territory of Ukraine equipment could not have
территории Украины техника же не могла
come from Russia though
приехать из России правда
I think somewhere somehow it was driving maybe that is to say
я думаю там где-то как-то ехало возможно
Russia did supply its
а то есть Россия всё-таки поставляла
own Well
свои Да
maybe somehow somehow
ну может как-то как-то
there on the sly somehow not Well what and
там в тихаря да как-то не Ну а что а
why well they supply you but look
почему ну вам-то поставляют но смотри
wait and we can say that you are
подожди а мы можем сказать что вот вы
blocking how is it
заперечиваете как это
in Russian deny Ukrainization two come on
по-русски отрицае украинизация два давай
come on
давай
you deny that we are at war with
вы отрицаете что мы воем со странами
NATO countries yes they are also mercenaries to you or not
НАТО да они тоже вам наёмники или нет
no look look  we are official I do not
нет смотри смотри мы официально Не
explain we are an official state they
объясняю мы официальное государство они
can
по стату ООН могут государству на
supply weapons to the state they attacked according to the UN
которое напали поставлять оружие есть в
statute there is a clearly written UN statute: "Ukraine is a
статуте ООН чётко прописано: "Украина-
sovereign state it and other
государство суверенное ей и другие
sovereign states can provide
суверенные государства могут оказывать
assistance with equipment" yes yes Russia
помощь техникой" да есть россия же
supplied
поставляла
equipment not to some states but
технику не государствам каким-то а
simply to some people in the territory of
просто каким-то людям на территории
Donetsk and Lugansk regions Russia did not
Донецкой и Луганской области россия не
recognize any DPR LPR true yes
признавала никакой ДНР ЛНР правда
that was a jamb that is the difference yes that is it
вот да это был косяк вот вот разница да
turns out
то есть получается
look a UN member state can be
смотри государству члену ООН можно
helped yes because it is written in the statute it is like this
помогать да потому что это в статуте он
No it is not like that well
написано это такое Нет это не такое ну
look stop again well such well
смотри стоп ещё раз ну такое ну
international law here is a mess
международное право тут же замес такой
seriously no no well wait stop you
ну серьёзно нет нет ну подожди стоп ты
you already see you have already started to back away
ты уже видишь ты уже стал назад пятиться
yes I told you clearly countries of the world are
да я тебе чётко сказал страны ээ мира
now helping Ukraine why because it is
сейчас помогают Украине почему потому
written in the UN statute it is
что так прописано в статуте ООН это есть
international law a country that was
международное право страна которая
subjected to aggression yes it can be
подверглась агрессии да ей можно
helped it is not something bad on
помогать это не есть чем-то плохим это
the contrary it contributes to its protection yes everything is
наоборот способствует её защите да всё
clear and  that's why Russia is helping us,
чётко и нам поэтому и помогают россия же
what did Russia do? It supplied weapons,
что делала россия поставляла оружие
soldiers, and money to the territory of certain
солдат и деньги на территорию отдельных
areas of the Luhansk and Donetsk regions of
районов Луганской и Донецкой области
Ukraine, yes, and this is precisely contrary to the
Украины да а это как раз противоречит
UN statute, this is an international
статуту ООН это есть международное
crime, and by the way, this is all
преступление и кстати это всё
recorded in the
зафиксировано в
European Assembly of the OSCE, it is recorded, well, I
ээской ассамблее ОБСЕ зафиксировано ну я
understand, yes, in UN resolutions, well, agree, really, well, well, well,
понимаю да в резолюциях ООН ну согласись
such a mess has
правда ну да ну ну тут такой замес
started, well, we can, okay, we won't anymore,
начался ну мы можем ладно не будем уже
look, look, in international law, it's not the
смотри смотри в международном праве не
Americans in Iraq, in international law, there is no
американцы в Ираке в международном праве
concept of a mess, there is no concept of a mess, what,
нет понятие замес нет понятия замес чем
look, I don't live in Iraq and I don't live in America, I live in Ukraine,
смотри я не живу в Ираке и я не живу в
which was
Америке я живу в Украине на которую
attacked by Russia, and you don't live in Iraq and in
напала Россия и ты живёшь не в Ираке и в
America, yes, we, uh, you're Russian, I'm Ukrainian,
Америке да мы ээ ты россиянин я украинец
so don't go to Japan, Iraq, in short,
поэтому не съезжай на Японию Ирак короче
some kind of okay, let me ask you this
какой-то там хорошо давай я тебе такой
question, let's ask you this one, that's
вопрос задам давай давай вот такой ну
also a serious question for you, how did it
тоже тебе серьёзный вопрос вот как
happen that way, that's
случилось так что вот
Russia, well, I mean, Russia is the
вот Россия ну я имею в виду Россия - это
European part of Russia, that's it, well, that's it,
европейская часть России это вот ну вот
Belarus and Ukraine, yes, that's it  how did it
ну вот Беларусь и Украина да вот как так
happen that now they gave Belarus
стало что сейчас вот дали Белоруси
nuclear weapons and they just want to
ядерное оружие а вас хотят просто
disarm you and generally limit you well yes well
разоружить и вообще вам ограничить вас
maybe you can do that yes I'll
вот ну да вот может вы до такого да
explain look Belarus is now
объясняю смотри Беларусь сейчас
under Russian occupation
находится под российской оккупацией
yes Belarus now
да Беларусь сейчас
this Lukashenko is arguing with Putin
этот Лукашенко срётся с Путиным
right uh no look Belarus
правильно ээ нет смотри Белоруссия
is under Russian occupation yes
находится под российской оккупацией да
it is completely dependent on
она находится в полной зависимости от
Russia absolutely right yes how come they did
России абсолютно верно да как это её в
n't accept it into BRICS just-just-just
БРИКС не принимали вот только-только
-just like they barely accepted
только-только вроде как еле-еле приняли
BRICS
БРИК
that's how it is under occupation that's what it's
вот как это под оккупацией так так и
called under occupation and what well well
называется под оккупацией и что ну вот
take Abkhazia is also under
ээ возьми абхазия находится тоже под
Russian occupation no one even calls it into BRICS though there have
российской оккупацией её тоже в БРИКС
been some recent squabbles with Abkhazia yeah they are
тёрки были недавно да они там вот это
buying this North oh South Ossetia the so
покупа Северная ой Южная Осетия так
called Samochab region is under
называемая регион самочаб находится под
Russian occupation yeah they are not accepting into any BRICS
оккупацией России да ни в какой брикс не
uh Transnistria Moldova
принимают ээ Приднестровье Молдовия
is under Russian occupation they are
находится под российской оккупацией ни в
not accepting into any BRICS true
какой брикс не принимает правда
and what does Ukraine not want to join BRICS why what is
а что Украина в БРИКС не хочет а зачем
BRICS anyway
что такое вообще БРИКС
well  can you decipher BRICS freedoms
ну можешь расшифровать брикс свобод
free trade zone can you
свободная торговая зона можешь
decipher the abbreviation where there are no
расшифровать абревиту где никаких
tariffs where everything is
тарифов нету где вот всё
mutually beneficial can you decipher the
взаимовыгодно можешь можешь расшифруй
word BRICS
слово брикс
well BCS is Brazil
ну бкс - это Бразилия
Russia Br and India China
Россия Бр и Индия Китай
and BRICS well and uh North Korea South
и Брикс ну и э Северная Корея южная
South Africa has also joined and
Южная Африка там ещё подсоединилась а
what is it with if South Africa why with
что она с если Южная Африка почему с
BRICS and not BRUX well that's how it
брикс а не брю
works well how does it work
ну вот так вот ну как так получается
if if it's South South Africa South
если если это южная Южная Африка южная
Africa yeah well I don't
Африка да ну
know wait look Brazil
ну вот не знаю подожди смотри бразилия
Russia India China all the letters match and the
Россия Индия Китай все буквы совпали и
last letter is S and you say South
последняя буква С и ты говоришь Южная
Africa I do
Африка
n't know well google it if you're interested well
не знаю ну погугли если интересно ну
why BRICS South Africa yeah with the letter S at the
почему БРКС Южна Африка да на букву С в
end and not U haven't thought about it well
конце а не на Ю не задумывался над этим
let's think for the sake of interest yeah well
ну давай подумаем ради интереса да ну
let's google it I don't know maybe it's still
давай погуглим я не знаю может всё-таки
North yeah not to me honestly I'm not interested by the way by
Северная да не мне честно не интересно я
the way I'll have to google Well there are a
кстати кстати надо будет погу Ну там ещё
bunch of other countries still Argentina
куча стран ещё Аргентина
still South Africa letter a what why
ещё Южная Африка буква а что почему
Why doesn't Ukraine want to join BC and  well
Почему Украина не хочет в БК а хорошо
what does BRICS offer us what is
что предлагает нам БРИКС что вот
interesting what Russia got from BRICS
интересно что Россия получила от БРКС
free free trade no not
свободная свободная торговля нет не
free trade is
свободная торговля
mutually beneficial
взаимовыгодна
investments you have China with Brazil there are
инвестиции у вас Китаем с Бразилием есть
duties no there are duties
пошли есть пошлины нет есть пошлины
between Russia Brazil Russia China
между Россией Бразилией Россией Китаем
yes Russia and India duties there no there
да Россией и Индией пошлины есть там нет
minimal there no no there
там минимальные там нет нет там чтобы
just to balance no no Japanese as
просто уравновесить нуни не японские как
I will explain look what is BRICS look
я объясню смотри что такое брикс смотри
BRICS BRICS is just a platform to talk once a
БРИКС брикс - это просто площадка раз в
year that's
год поговорить вот и
all I understand it is developing but look
всё я понимаю она развивается но смотри
if we look yes for example the UN the UN has a
если мы смотрим да например ООН ООН есть
headquarters there are organizational
штаб-квартира есть организационные
structures and so on this is an
структуры и так дальше вот это
international organization and where is the
международная организация а где
BRICS headquarters there is at least
штаб-квартира БРИКС вот есть хотя бы
some BRICS Office where some
какой-то Офикс БРИКС где сидит какая-то
secretary sits are going to get together yes there no no well
секретар собираются собираются да там
about Zeros we look well the dollar is
нет нет ну про Нули мы смотрим ну доллар
already well it is an unreliable currency well and in
уже ну это ненадёжная валюта да ну а в
what to in what in what currencies are you
каких до в какой в каких валютах вы
calculated well
рассчитые
we already
ну у нас уже зависимость от
had a 75% dependence on the dollar now in what
доллара была 75% сейчас уже какой
currency  what currency do you use to pay with India
валютой выи какой валютой вы с Индии
national currencies what well
национальными валютами какими
they have their brahmas rupi ru they
ну они своими там брахмами рупи ру они
pay you rupees you pay them rubles and
вам платят рупи вы им платите рубли а
where do you put these rupees then well they have
куда вы деваете потом эти рупи ну у них
good medicine there they have Wait
там у них хорошая медицина у них Подожди
look no look India bought something from you
смотри не вот смотри Индия что-то у вас
paid you rupees if it
купила заплатила вам рупи если бы она
paid you that's the point of the dollar
вам заплатила вот в чём суть доллара вы
for example you got dollars from India bought
например у Индии получили доллары купили
something from Switzerland for dollars yes for
у Швейцарии что-то за доллары да
example and what and from whom do you buy for
например а что вы и у кого купите за
rupees
рупи
not we pay with them we have well we
не мы с ними рассчитываемся у нас ну
interact
взаимодаём
they sell to us yes well look you sell to them you
они нам продают да ну смотрите вы им вы
sell to them more than they sell to you so with you
им продаёте больше чем они вам так у вас
India for example yes that is it turns out you
Индии например да то есть получается вы
sell to them uh they give you a bunch of rupees
им продаёте ээ они вам дают кучу рупи
where do you put these rupees well how is it there maybe there is some
куда вы эти рупи деваете
crypto there
ну там как там может крипта там что-то
all this is behind maybe somehow well
вот это всё там заде может как-то там ну
I don't know somehow all this is there am I
я не знаю как-то всё это там заму я
right I understand correctly you
правильно я правильно понимаю вы
received for example 200 million dollars in
получили например там 200 млн долларов в
rupee equivalent and these  200 million someone
рупе эквиваленте и эти 200 млн кто-то у
buys rupees from you to invest in crypto
вас рупи покупает чтобы вложить в крипту
here himself well as far as I understand the very
тут сам сам ну насколько я понимаю сам
meaning of the development of BRICS is an alternative an
смысл развития БРИКС - это альтернатива
alternative to the dollar an alternative to the euro to
альтернатива доллару альтернатива евро
make a free trade economic
сделать свободную торговой экономическую
zone that will be
зону которая будет
calculated will be like approximately
рассчитываться будет будет как примерно
look how it is not now not now
смотри как это не сейчас не сейчас
now don't tell me this at all
сейчас это вообще не говори мне это
now in the initial path it will
сейчас в начальном пути это будет
develop like approximately the
развиваться так примерно как
European Union there will be one national currency
Евросоюз будет одна национальная валюта
and it will be in will be beneficial to each other to
и будет в будет выгодно друг другу
develop you understand stop stop I got it I got it
развивать понимаешь стоп стоп я я понял
I'm right it is beneficial for us to develop India It is
я правильно нам выгодно развивать Индию
beneficial for India to develop Russia It is
Индии выгодно развивать Россию России
beneficial for Russia I got it let's
выгодно понял давай
mutually beneficial we don't fix anyone
взаимовыгодное никого не фиксируем
now no uh rupees shmupii no now
сейчас никаких ээ рупи шмупий нет сейчас
you still trade for dollars a lady well bye bye yes damn bye bye yes
вы всё-таки за баксы торгуете даму
unfortunately it will still be yes it will still be a
сожалению это будет ещё да это будет ещё
long time understood then another question well I
долго понял тогда другой вопро ну я
hope another question five years and
надеюсь другой вопрос лет пять а лет
five years I understand correctly that in
пять я правильно понимаю что через лет
five years some national
пять появится какая-то национальная
currency will appear in Brazil Russia India China and
валюта у Бразилии России Индии Китая и
South Africa one
Южной Африки одна
common common well how
общая общая
I don't know how it is how they
ну как я не знаю как это как они это
want it well I  I can roughly imagine that it
хотят ну я примерно представляю что это
will be like this, yes, well,
будет так да
everyone has something to sell to each other,
ну у у всех есть что друг другу продать
sell to buy, and it will be beneficial for everyone to
продать купить и всем будет выгодно друг
develop each other, everyone has the potential, the
друга развивать у всех есть потенциал
potential to develop each other now
потенциал друг друга развивать теперь
tell me, uh, how much of China's economy does
скажи ээ сколько в экономике Китая
trade turnover with Russia amount to, what
товарооборот с Россией составляет
percent,
сколько процентов
half 2%, well, much much less than with
пол2% ну намного намного меньше чем с
America, yes, that is, look, China, its
Америкой да то есть смотри Китай у него
main trading partner is Europe and the
основной торговый партнёр - это Европа и
USA, so why does America
США так ну а зачем Америка их
start them, look, China's entire trade turnover
нача смотри у Китая весь товарооборот -
is Europe and the USA, these are huge markets,
это Европа и США это огромные рынки
Russia is in this market 2%, what do you think,
россия в этом рынке 2% как ты думаешь
will China, uh, let's say, give up the
будет ли Китай э-э скажем отказываться
markets of the USA and Europe in order to
от рынков США и Европы для того чтобы
integrate something with Russia,
интегрироваться что-то там с Россией
which buys only 2% from it,
которая у неё покупает только 2%
well, what should it do if Trump is like this,
ну а что ему делать если Трамп такие вот
if he led
если он вёл
such, let's go, what, look, the trick is that the trick is that the
такие пошли что смотри фишка в
duty is who
том фишка в том что такое пошлина кто
pays the
платит за
duty, they and they get, uh,
пошлину те и те получают э покупатели
American buyers, that is, American
американские то есть американские
buyers will pay, let's go, yes, China,
покупатели будут платить пошли да Китай
and they will suffer, yes, the manufacturers,
а и а страдать будут да производители
China, as not China, have been producing and
китай как не Китай как производил так и
producing, well, look, yes,
производил ну смотри да ну рынок сбыта у
they have no market  America listen Americans won't
них нет америка слушай американцы не
stop buying phones won't
перестанут покупать телефоны не
stop buying clothes but they
перестанут покупать шмотки да они всё
won't do it anyway everything
равно же не будут это делать всё у себя
will be more expensive at home that's how it is more expensive
буду дороже покупать вот так вот дороже
yes they will simply pay more the
да просто будут они платить дороже
Americans will build China will
американцы будут строить Китаю будут всё
anyway the question now uh even uh the trick is
равно вопрос теперь ээ даже э фишка в
that with America there is such a trade turnover
том что с Америкой такой товарооборот
that it is profitable to work with them even with these duties
что с ней выгодно даже с этими пошлинами
but with Russia Russia is poor
работать а с Россией Россия бедная
Russia is poor and it buys little because
Россия бедная и она покупает мало потому
it can't afford what the
что она не может себе позволить то что
Americans and Europeans allow you to
позволяют се американцы и европейцы
agree I do
согласись
n't know Andryukha we have just a ton of Chinese cars
не знаю Андрюх у нас тачек китайских
I just don't know why people
просто киши просто я не знаю зачем люди
buy this crap but they are beautiful they are I'm
это [__] берут но они красивые они я
telling you well only Chinese I'm
тебе говорю ну одни китайские я по
driving around Krasnodar in my
Краснодару вот еду на своей
Toyota well it's already 15
Тойоте ну уже ей 15
years old and there are brand new all Chinese
лет и вот прямо новенькие всё китайские
and all kinds there are not all shiny there are
и каких только нету все там блестят там
only Chinese cars shimmering I don't
переливаются одни китайские машины я не
know why people buy this I wouldn't buy something like that
знаю зачем люди это берут я бы такое не
But they buy they buy they buy I'm telling you the whole
Но берут берут берут я тебе говорю весь
city is in these Chinese cars I
город в этих китайских машинах
understand in short in general they buy come on  let's
понял короче в общем берут давай
summarize
подрезюмируем
now BRICS will create its own currency and that's it
сейчас БРИКС создаст свою валюту и все
Russia not now nothing in 5 years oh that's
Россия не сейчас нече через 5 лет ой это
in the best case in the best case but I
в лучшем случае в лучшем а
understand in short or else or even more yes that's a
понял короче а то а то и больше да это
long-term pissing game
долгосрочно вилами по воде писа
yes join BRICS guys
да присоединяйтесь до БРИКС ребята
enough of you look we're waiting we're we're
хватит вас смотри мы ждём мы мы же
Ukrainians are cunning we're joining those
украинцы хитрые мы присоединяемся к тем
who have already made their own currency for example the
кто уже сделал свою валюту вот например
European Union made its own currency that's all we want to join the
Евросоюз сделал свою валюту всё мы хотим
European Union you will make the BRICS currency let's think about it
в Евросоюз вы сделаете валюту БРИКС
but while you don't have a currency while
подумаем а пока у вас нет валюты пока у
you only have talk why
вас только разговоры зачем к вам
join you if there is the euro really so
присоединяться если есть евро правда так
together we will make the currency no no we're
вместе будем делать валюту не не мы же
cunning why should we do it on equal
хитры зачем нам делать на равных
terms we can already and you are like
условиях мы можем уже а вы такие себе
when will we do everything you
когда мы всё сделаем вы
oh you are cunning yes we we also waited for the European Union
Ох вы хитрые да мы мы также к Евросоюзу
until they did everything make the
дождались пока они всё сделают сделают
euro now we're joining yes that's it all
евро теперь присоединяемся да всё весь
this way and here make BRICS and
этот путь та так и тут сделайте брикс а
we'll see mm where is it better to
мы посмотрим мм где лучше к евро
join the euro or the BCS currency and by the way
присоединиться или к валюте БКС а кстати
what will the BCS currency be called oh oh I don't
как будет называться валюта БКС ой ой не
know  a cart maybe BRICS will be like that
знаю бричка может брикс такая будет
maybe a cart one cart like two carts
может бричка одна бричка типа две брички
10 carts that's what they'll call it well how well
10 бричек так и будут называть ну как ну
a thousand as you call it there that's your
тыся как у вас называют там это ваша
hryvnia for us well 1,000 a thousand is 500 rubles a five-hat
гривны у нас ну 1.000 косарь 500 руб
there I don't know 5,000 well 5,000
пятихатка там я не знаю 5.000 ну 5.000
5,000 there a hundred there I don't
5.000 там стольник
know they also call it 1,000 rubles there
там не знаю ещё называют 1.000 рубль там
5 rubles that means 5,000 well that's it that's it
5 руб это значит 5.000 ну вот так вот
in Slang I don't know what you
тако на слнге я не знаю как у вас там
call it there it's just seems to me that by the time
называется просто мне кажется что пока
you introduce this currency BRICS you'll no longer have
вы введёте эту валюту БРКС у вас уже
thousands there but millions there will be
будут не тысячи там а миллионы ходить
five-hat I do
пятилям будет
n't know now everyone will be shaken up and how anyone will
не знаю сейчас всех тряхнёт а как кто
survive we'll see now
там выживет посмотрим сейчас трясти
everyone will be shaken up well okay look let's run
будет всех ну хорошо смотрите побежал
meet up when there will be a BRICS currency that's the
встретимся когда будет валюта БРИКС
footage yes there is a currency BRICS no well
вот это кадры да есть валюта Брикс не ну
Rupiah yes Rupin well for now in dollars yes yes that's how
Рупи да Рупин ну пока в долларе дада да
they all are when you start them according to the
вот так они все когда их начинаешь по
facts yes Minsk yes  Minsk agreements
фактам да Минские да Минские соглашения
Ukraine signed and you took and
можно украина подписала а вы взяли
captured violated Minsk agreements
и захватили нарушили Минские соглашения
and BRICS and there is no BRICS and
да брикс а а нету никакого брикса да а
some kind of turnover of China with Russia
какой-то оборот Китая с России
when Androni's father starts asking them about the facts it
когда отец Андрони их по фактам начинает
turns out they: "Where are your trump
спрашивать оказывается у них: "Где ваши
cards?" As Trump said: "No trump card
козыри?" Как говорил Трамп: "Нету козыря
is blew" like subscribe comment subscribe
это блев" лайк подписка комент підпишись
to my Instagram I don't know why
на мій Instagram я не знаю для чго це
you do this why else are you there to watch on
тобі для чого ще тобі там дивитись на
Face but for you it's one two or three
Face але для тебе це один два або три
clicks you support me and I will say:
клика підтримаєш мене и я буду казати:
"Wow I have a bunch of followers and I
"Вау в мене там купа фоловерів и в мене
will be cool
буде класний
tune in to my Instagram pop Andrey"
настроись на мій Instagram попик Андрей"
so let me see you
отак давай я тебя очю